A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A94), 1966-1994; 1.20; 217.2 Cubic Feet; Record cartons R2728-R2895, R2880A, R2896-R2902, R2905, R2906-R2911, R9402 and R9403.
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - EO 9036 - National Puerto Rican Coalition, Inc. - Persistence of poverty in Puerto Rican community - Supplementary material (Box R2832)
    - EO 9038 - Community Foundation Conference on Youth Development - Youth Future Conference, 1990-1992 (Box R2832)
    - EO 9039 - Mexican American Legal Defense and Eductional Fund - Hispanic Community Support, 1990-1994 (Box R2832)
    - EO 9040 - Southern Regional Council - Technical assistance to minorities, 1990-1992 (Box R2832)
    - EO 9041 - Institute for Puerto Rican Policy - Latino initiatives redistricting, 1990-1993 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9042 - Urban Institute - Testing discrimination conference, 1990-1993 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9043 - Development Training Institute - Data base workforce analysis, 1990-1992 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9101 - Leadership Conference Education Fund - Redistricting and minorities, 1990-1991 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9104 - Parents United for the D.C. Public Schools - Networking and Research, 1990 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9105 - National Congress for Community Economic Development - Service Development Initiative, 1989-1992 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9106 - Fair Employment Council of Greater Washington, 1990-1993 (Box R2833)
    - EO 9107 - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies - Minority males initiative, 1990-1993 (Box R2834)
    - EO 9110 - Center for Community Change - Poverty issues education, 1990-1992 (Box R2834)
    - EO 9112 - Center for Community Change - Newsletter insert, 1991-1992 (Box R2834)
    - EO 9115 - People for the American Way - Racial Tensions in the United States, 1990-1993 (Box R2834)
    - EO 9116 - National Association for Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Special Contribution Fund - Conference Statements, 1991-1992 (Box R2834)
    - EO 9117 - Leadership Conference Education Fund - Civil rights education campaign, 1991-1994 (Box R2834)
    - EO 9118 - Urban Institute - Discrimination in hiring report, 1990-1992; 3 folders. (Box R2835)
    - EO 9120 - Yale University - Social welfare policy book, 1991-1993 (Box R2835)
    - EO 9125 - Philantropic Initiative - New donor reconnaissance Phase II, 1990-1993 (Box R2835)
    - EO 9127 - National Association of Latino Elected and Appointed Officials Educational Fund - Public Policy Information, 1989-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2836)
    - EO 9129 - Center for Employment Training - Learning in Context, 1991-1993 (Box R2836)
    - EO 9131 - Northwestern University - Minority employment project, 1991-1992 (Box R2836)
    - EO 9133 - Hispanics in Philanthropy - Operating expenses, 1987-1994 (Box R2836)
    - EO 9134 - Yale University - Child development and community police, 1991-1993 (Box R2837)
    - EO 9135 - Center for Documentary Media - Documentary on poverty in America, 1991 (Box R2837)
    - EO 9141 - Urban Institute - Testing to measure discrimination activities - Supplementary material, 1991-1993 (Box R2837)
    - EO 9143 - Parents United for the DC Public Schools - D.C. Committee on Public Education, 1991-1992 (Box R2837)
    - EO 9144 - Piton Foundation - School reform in Denver, 1991-1993 (Box R2837)
    - EO 9145 - Fair Employment Council of Greater Washington - Latino discriminatory employment practice testing initiative, 1991-1993 (Box R2837)
    - EO 9146 - Center for Community Change - Newsletters in philantropic publications, 1991-1993 (Box R2838)
    - EO 9147 - HandsNet - Electronic network feasibility, 1989-1994 (Box R2838)
  - Global Environment (GE)
    - GE 9001 - Earth Day 1990 - Expansion Activities, 1990-1991 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9002 - African Centre for Technology Studies - Global Warming Conference, 1990-1993 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9003 - Scientific Committee on Problems of the Environment - Land Use, 1990-1991 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9004 - Consultative Group on Biological Diversity (CGBD) - Program Activities, 1989-1992 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9005 - Princeton University - Summer School, 1990-1993 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9006 - Environmental and Energy Institute - Parliamentarians Travel Expenses, 1990 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9007 - National Academy of Engineering Fund - Workshop for Chlorofluorocarbon Substitution Technology Transfer, 1985, 1990-1992 (Box R2838)
    - GE 9008 - Rocky Mountain Institute - BELLE Phase I, 1990-1992 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9009 - World Meteorological Organization - Panel Travel Expenses, 1990-1991 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9010 - Tufts University - Environmental Management Conference, 1989-1991 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9011 - Climate Institute - Policy briefings, 1989-1991 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9012 - Women USA Fund, Inc. - Women's Global Participation, 1990-1992 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9013 - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) Demonstration Project with USSR GOSSTROI, 1989-1992 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9014 - Hainan Province - Economic Development and Environment Conference, 1990 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9019 - People's University of China - Environmental economics - translation, 1990-1993 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9020 - Environmental Defense Fund - International accord on climate change, 1988-1992 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9021 - Conservation International - Ecosystem Conservation Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box R2839)
    - GE 9022 - China Initiative, 1990-1993 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9024 - Ghandi Institute of Development Research - Global Commons, 1990-1993 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9026 - International Institute for Energy Conservation - Energy Efficient Refrigerator development, 1990-1992 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9028 - World Bank - Workshop on environmental impact of coal use in China, 1990-1992 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9029 - University of California - Hastings College of the Law - Conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9030 - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Greenhouse gas emissions in India, 1990-1993 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9031 - Committee of Soviet Scientists - 21st Century Leadership Program, 1990-1993 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9032 - Tata Energy Research Institute - Washington, D. C. office, 1990-1992 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9033 - Conservation International - Tropical forest products, 1990-1991 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9035 - Biomass Users Network - Sugarcane to energy technologies, 1990-1993 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9036 - Cornell University - Golobal environment accords with Brazil, 1990-1993 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9038 - Asia Society - Environmental activism in Asia, 1990-1992 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9039 - Institute of Amazon Studies - Brazilian Amazon Conference, 1990-1992 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9041 - Social Science Research Council - Global Environmental change conference, 1990-1992 (Box R2840)
    - GE 9102 - Resources Development Foundation - Energy Supply and transmissions systems, 1990-1993 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9104 - Climate lnstitute - Global Climate change impact, 1990-1993 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9105 - CulturalSurvival, Inc. - Trading efforts evaluation and expansion, 1991 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9106 - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis - Scholar participation, 1991 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9107 - Commonwealth Science Council - Cassava workshop, 1991-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9108 - Institute for 21st Century Studies - Ibadan workshop, 1991 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9111 - Conservation International Foundation - Conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9112 - Institute for Local Self-Reliance - Plant matter-based production, 1990-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9114 - Energy Conversion Devices - Photo-voltaic lanterns distribution, 1991-1994 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9115 - University of Ilorin - Forest Reserve Program in Nigeria, 1990-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9116 - BRASCEP Engenharia, Ltda. - Biomass technology, 1991-1993 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9117 - New York Rainforest Alliance, Inc. - Non-timber forest products, 1991 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9121 - Mexico City Office of General Coordination of Environmental Projects - Toxic waste disposal, 1991-1993 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9123 - Institute Autonomo de Investigaciones Ecologias, A.C. - Conference and environmental awareness training program, 1990-1993 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9124 - University of Sao Paulo - Groundwater pollution courses, 1990-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9125 - Social Justice Committee of Montreal - Debt and environment program, 1990-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9126 - International Institute for Environment and Development - Biomass study, 1991-1993 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9127 - Global Tomorrow Coalition - LDC assembly participation, 1991 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9128 - Centre for Applied Studies in International Negotiations (CASIN) - Seminar, 1991-1992 (Box R2841)
    - GE 9129 - Centro de Investigaciones Sociales, Ambientales y Tecnologicas - Conference, 1991-1993 (Box R2842)
    - GE 9131 - Centro de Investigaciones Sociales, Ambientales y Tecnologicas - Seminar on Sustainable Development, 1991-1993 (Box R2842)
    - GE 9133 - Conservation Law Foundation - Energy efficient hotel designs, 1991-1993 (Box R2842)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - HS 8717 - UN/WHO - Intersectoral action for health - Project proposals, 1986-1993 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8891 - Nursing Education - Conference, 1988-1989 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8909 - University of Hawaii - Tropical Medicine Annual Meeting, 1988-1990 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8921 - Johns Hopkins University - Guillain-Barre Syndrome in China, 1988-1991 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8927 - Cornell University - China Health Project, 1988-1990 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8932 - University of Hawaii (Manoa) - Blood-Stage Malaria Vaccine Adjuvant, 1987-1993 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8934 - Harvard University - Psychiatric Care in China, 1988-1992 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8964 - University of Leeds - "Primary Mother Care" Illustration, 1989-1993 (Box R2842)
    - HS 8965 - Institute of Tropical Medicine - HIV infection factors, 1988-1992 (Box R2842)
    - HS 9001 - Yale University - Molecular epidemiology of dengue viruses, 1987-1992 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9003 - University of Benin (Togo) - Demography and Health Planning, 1989-1993 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9006 - Brigham and Women's Hospital Visceral Leishmaniasis in Brazil, 1986-1991 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9007- University of Michigan - Respiratory Synctytial Vaccine, 1989-1993 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9009 - International Society for Infectious Diseases - Congress, 1990-1992 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9011 - American Society for Circumpolar Health - Aveolar Echinococcosis, 1989-1991 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9014 - Jackson Foundation (for the Advancement of Military Medicine) - Parasitic Zoonoses Conference, 1988-1993 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9015 - Population Council - Microcomputer Software System for Thailand and Indonesia, 1989-1991 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9016 - McMaster University - University Partnerships in Essential Health Research, 1989-1991 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9017 - Emory University - Training Course, 1989-1991 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9018 - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Vaccine Conferences, 1984-1992 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9019 - American College of Physicians - International Health Action Programs, 1989-1992 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9020 - ETV Productions of South Carolina, Inc. - "The Planned Miracle", 1990-1992 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9021 - University of Ibadan - Ibrapa Community Health Program Research Capabilities, 1988-1993 (Box R2843)
    - HS 9027 - Harvard University - Health Transition Workshop proceedings, 1990-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9029 - University of Dar es Salaam - Muhimbili Medical Center Laboratory, 1989-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9030 - Gadjah Mada University - Study with Yale on Bronchial Asthma, 1989-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9031 - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF) - World Summit for Children, 1990-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9033 - Universityof California (San Diego) - Institute of Biomedical Science, 1990-1991 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9037 - Harvard University - Outpatient Hospitals meeting, 1990-1991 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9039 - American Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene - Annual meeting, 1989-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9041 - Johns Hopkins University - Ada, 1987-1991 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9042 - Oral Rabies - Conference, 1990-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9045 - Johns Hopkins University - Perez-Morga, 1988-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9046 - McGill University - Health care of Ethiopians, 1990-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9047 - Children's Vaccine Initiative - Conference meals and accomodations costs, 1990-1991 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9049 - African Medical and Research Foundation, USA - Sexuality and Health in Sub-Saharan Africa publication, 1990-1993 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9050 - Task Force for Child Survival - Conference, 1989-1992 (Box R2844)
    - HS 9102 - Harvard University - Diarrheal disease study, 1990-1992 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9106 - National Academy of Sciences - Microbial threats to health, 1990-1992 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9107 - National Institute for Medical Research - Conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9108 - McKinney, Jeff, 1990-1991 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9109 - Gadjah Mada University - Dengue Haemorrhagic Fever, 1990-1992 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9111 - University of California (San Francisco) - Child survival programs, 1989-1992 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9113 - Program tor Appropriate Technology in Health (PATH) - Epstein Barr Virus meeting, 1990-1991 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9114 - National Council for International Health (NCIH) - 1991 Annual Conference, 1986-1992 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9115 - International Health and Biomedicine, Ltd. - Photographic Exhibition, 1991 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9116 - Khon Kaen University - Dengue hemorrhagic fever treatment, 1990-1991 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9117 - Educational Commission for Foreign Medical Graduates, 1989-1992 (Box R2845)
    - HS 9118 - Rasheed, Fawzia N., 1990-1993 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9121 - United Nations - World Health Organization - Public Health systems newsletter, 1986-1993 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9122 - Program for Appropriate Technology in Health (PATH) - Hepatitis B conference, 1990-1992 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9125 - Ministry of Public Health (Cameroon) - Epidemiology Board site visits, 1991 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9127 - Carvajal Foundation - Program evaluation, 1989-1993 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9129 - Texas Tech University Health Sciences center - Post-shigella nutritional management, 1991-1993 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9131 - Johns Hopkins University - Chinese Paralytic Syndrome, 1991-1993 (Box R2846)
    - HS 9133 - Mahidol University - 1991 Congress of Medical Virology (Box R2847)
    - HS 9134 - Johns Hopkins University - Disease Control Workshop Series, 1991-1994 (Box R2847)
    - HS 9138 - Umversity of Western Australia - Virus newsletter, 1986-1992 (Box R2847)
    - HS 9141 - University of Yaounde - Health technology conference, 1990-1992 (Box R2847)
    - HS 9143 - International Society for Infectious Diseases - Congress in Kenya, 1991-1992 (Box R2847)
    - HS 9146 - University of Surrey - Japanese encephalitis vaccine, 1990-1992 (Box R2847)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - PS 8715 - National University of Singapore - Maternal morality in South East Asia - Conference, 1986-1993 (Box R2847)
    - PS 8741 - Marine Biological Laboratory (Woods Hole) - Fertilization symposium, 1986-1989 (Box R2847)
    - PS 8833 - Peking University - Population training, 1987-1993 (Box R2847)
    - PS 8838 - University of Southern California - Mexican TV & family planning effects, 1988-1993 (Box R2847)
    - PS 8906 - Society for Women and AIDS in Africa - Conference, 1989, 1992 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8907 - Bejing Medical University - Medical demography training, 1986-1992 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8917 - Centro de Estudios Urbanos y Regionales - Fertility patterns in Argentina, 1987-1990 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8918 - Women Judges Fund for Justice - Reproductive Technology and Law Conference, 1988-1990. 1993 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8920- University of Nairobi - Progestins and Malaria, 1988-1993 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8921 - Population Council, Inc. - HIV Vectors in the reproductive tract, 1989-1994 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8923 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - Conference, 1989-1990 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8926 - Assiut University - Norplant Use, 1985-1993 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8933 - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Abortion and unmarried Chinese women, 1989, 1993 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8936 - Applied Population Research Trust (India) - Indian Population, 1988-1993 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8937 - Columbia University - Oral rehydration in India, 1989-1991 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8940 - University of Michigan - Marriage, Family, and fertility in China, 1988-1993 (Box R2848)
    - PS 8942 - International Center for Research on Women - Family Structure in developing countries, 1989-1992 (Box R2849)
    - PS 8943 - Johns Hopkins University - Sichuan, China sterilization study, 1988-1994 (Box R2849)
    - PS 8946 - Columbia University - Family planning programs of the developing world, 1985-1992 (Box R2849)
    - PS 8949 - Institute of Health, Sao Paulo - Diaphragm acceptability & use, 1988-1993 (Box R2849)
    - PS 8951 - University of Cordoba - Reproductive biology and endocrinology, 1987-1993 (Box R2849)
    - PS 8953 - Christian Medical College, Ludhiana - Female discrimination in North India hospitals, 1989-1992 (Box R2849)
    - PS 9002 - University of Siena - Spermatology conference, 1990 (Box R2850)
    - PS 9003 - Emory University - Family planning, 1989-1992 (Box R2850)
    - PS 9004 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - Latin American seminar, 1990 (Box R2850)
    - PS 9005 - Population Crisis Committee - Information kits for developing countries, 1988-1992 (Box R2850)
    - PS 9005 - Population Crisis Committee - Information kits for developing countries - Supplementary material (Box R2850)
    - PS 9006 - Princeton University - Birth spacing and infant health in the Philippines, 1989-1992 (Box R2850)
    - PS 9007 - Population Resource Center - Information programs, 1987-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2850)
    - PS 9008 - Catholic University - Endocrine role mammary gland, 1990 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9009 - National Academy of Sciences - Africans & population panel, 1989-1993 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9010 - Population Council, Inc. - Antifertility vaccine, 1988-1992 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9014 - Center for Population Options - Adolescent fertility conference, 1990 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9020 - University of Cuyo - Modern light microscopy & video workshop, 1990-1993 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9021 - University of Salzburg - Gossypol and Anti-LHRH vaccine, 1989-1993 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9022 - Program for Appropriate Technology in Health - Sexually tnansmitted diseases in Africa, 1989-1992 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9024 - Family Care International - Safe motherhood conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2851)
    - PS 9027 - Latin American Social Sciences Research Council - Population, 1985-1992 (Box R2852)
    - PS 9031 - Cornell University - Gossypol vaginal cream, 1990-1992 (Box R2852)
    - PS 9033 - University of Alabama - Vesico-vaginal fistula in Northern Nigeria, 1989-1992 (Box R2852)
    - PS 9035 - Population Council, Inc. - Sperm immobilizing factor, 1988-1992 (Box R2852)
    - PS 9036 - Princeton University - Demographic statistical models, 1988-1993 (Box R2852)
    - PS 9037 - Academia Mexicana de Investigacion en Demografia Medica - Maternal & child mortality in Latin America, 1990-1994 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9039 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population -Population libraries and Zimbabwe workshop, 1990-1992 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9040 - All-India Institute of Medical Sciences (New Delhi) - Reproductive physiology conference, 1990 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9041 - Moreno, Lorenzo, 1990-1992 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9044 - World Bank - Population programs in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1990-1991 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9047 - Task force to plan org. & eval. For introduction of new contraceptives in China, 1988-1992 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9102 - Psychoyos, Alexandre, 1980-1992 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9104 - National Institute of Nutrition Salvador Zubiran (Mexico City) - Latin Amer. meeting on human reoroduction, 1988, 1991-1992 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9106 - University of Pennsylvania - Scientific & ethical issues in reproduction conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2853)
    - PS 9109 - University of the Andes (Bogota) - Fertility transition in Colombia and Venezuela, 1989-1993 (Box R2854)
    - PS 9110 - Catholic University (Chile) - Spermatozoa in female tubal fluid, 1989-1994 (Box R2854)
    - PS 9111 - University of Chile - Human Corpus Luteum Function, 1985-1993 (Box R2854)
    - PS 9114 - Institute of Biology & Experimental Medicine (Buenos-Aires) - Follicular maturation, 1988-1992 (Box R2854)
    - PS 9119 - National Archives Trust Fund Board - Sanger Papers, 1989-1994 (Box R2855)
    - PS 9120 - Johns Hopkins University - Luteal angiogenic factor, 1989-1993 (Box R2855)
    - PS 9122 - International Women's Health Coalition - Reproductive tract infection, 1991-1993 (Box R2855)
    - PS 9123 - Family Care International - Maternal health services in Kenya, 1991-1993 (Box R2855)
    - PS 9124 - Al-Azhar University - Bioethics in human reproduction conference, 1991-1994 (Box R2855)
    - PS 9126 - Social Science Research Council - Population growth and environmental quality, 1991-1993 (Box R2855)
    - PS 9127 - Asociacion Dominicana Pro-Bienestar de la Familia, Inc. - Sexual experience and contracentive practices in Dominican Republic, 1990-1994 (Box R2855)
  - International Security (IS)
    - IS 9104 - Parliamentarians for Global Action - Nuclear Test ban and Peacekeeping, 1991-1993 (Box R2856)
    - IS 9105 - Institute of International Relations (Mozambique) - Southern Africa Conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2856)
    - IS 9106 - Nuclear Control Institute - Plutonium conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2856)
    - IS 9109 - Fund for Peace, Inc. - National Security Archive, 1991-1992 (Box R2856)
    - IS 9111 - Center for Foreign Policy Development - Cuba and Superpowers Conference, 1990-1993 (Box R2856)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 8734 - Rockefeller Archives and Research Center - Resident scholars in the history of philanthropy, 1987-1992 (Box R2856)
    - SIE 8815 - Duke University - Philanthropy and voluntarism, 1986-1993 (Box R2856)
    - SIE 8827 - Geneva - Graduate Institute of International Studies - AIDS networks, 1988-1991 (Box R2856)
    - SIE 8934 - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York, 1984-1991 (Box R2857)
    - SIE 8938 - Center for Women Policy Studies - Reproductive Laws for the 1990's, 1989-1993 (Box R2857)
    - SIE 8941 - Southern Connecticut State University - Training education leaders, 1989-1992 (Box R2857)
    - SIE 8961 - Bryant Park Restoration Corporation - Music & dance tickets booth, 1989-1993 (Box R2857)
    - SIE 8962 - Rutgers University - Abortion issue in 1989 election, 1989-1990 (Box R2857)
    - SIE 8963 - Investor Responsibility Research Center, Inc. - Global Environment information, 1989-1992 (Box R2857)
    - SIE 9001 - Rockefeller Foundation/MacArthur Foundation Task Force on the Future of the U.S.Defense Budget, 1989-1992 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9005 - Conflict Management Project - African workshop, 1990-1993 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9006 - Independent Sector - Studies in Leadership, 1990-1992 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9008 - Overseas Development Network, 1987-1993 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9008 - Overseas Development Network - Supplementary material (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9010- Institute of International Relations (Mozambique) - Mozambique & Southern Africa conference, 1989-1990 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9012 - Twentieth Century Fund - Combat drug abuse programs, 1989-1991 (Box R2858)